Guide to the J. B. Matthews Papers, 1862-1986 and undated
J. B. Matthews papers 1862-1986 and undated
- Persons Files Series, ca. 1920s-1980s, (58 boxes)
  - Bridges, Harry Renton, 1941-1950
  - Briggs, Austin, 1952
  - Brigham, Edward, 1956
  - Brindze, Ruth, undated
  - Brissenden, Paul F., undated
  - Brodsky, Joseph R., 1947
  - Bromberg, J. Edward, 1939
  - Bromfield, Louis, 1950
  - Brooks, Lawrence, undated
  - Brothers, L. F., 1955
  - Broun, Heywood, 1938
  - Browder, Earl, 1935-1945
  - Browder, Felix E., undated
  - Brown, Charlotte Hawkins, 1945-1947
  - Brcwn, Constantine (Liz), 1953
  - Brown, Funson Elmer, 1935-1950 (Box 595)
  - Brown, George E., 1941
  - Brown, Irving, 1952
  - Brown, Lloyd, 1946
  - Brown, Murray, 1938-1943
  - Brunauer, Esther, 1936
  - Brunauer, Stephen, 1948-1951
  - Bruno, Jack, 1946
  - Bryan, Helen R., 1945
  - Bryan, Julien, 1951
  - Bryson, Hugh, 1946-1950
  - Bryson, Lyman, 1946-1947
  - Buck, Pearl S., 1950-1957
  - Buckles, Harold H., undated
  - Budenz, Louis Francis, 1945-1952
  - Bunche, Ralph, undated
  - Burgess, Ernst W., 1941-1948
  - Burgum, Edwin Berry, 1940-1953
  - Burke, E.F., 1941-1946
  - Burke, Fielding, 1941
  - Burke, Thomas E., 1953-1954
  - Burnham, James, 1947
  - Burns, Frank, 1941
  - Burrows, Abe, 1950
  - Burt, Sam, 1943-1946
  - Burtt, Edwin A., undated
  - C, 1949, 1968
  - Cable, George W., 1946
  - Cacchione, Peter V., 1946
  - Cachin, Marcel, 1946
  - Calhern, Louis, 1945 (Box 596)
  - Calomiris, Angela, 1950
  - Cameron, Angus, 1947-1950
  - Cammer, Harold I., 1956
  - Campbell, Carleton, undated
  - Campbell, Persia, 1942
  - Campbell, Robert, 1946
  - Camplis, Richard, 1946
  - Caplan, Jonah E., 1950
  - Capp, A1, 1950-1961
  - Carawan, Guy, undated
  - Carey, James, 1940-1949
  - Carlisle, Harry, 1941
  - Carlson, Anton J., 1946-1956
  - Carlson, John Roy, 1936-1946
  - Carr, Sam, 1946
  - Carse, Robert, 1945
  - Carter, Edward C., 1941-1951
  - Carter, Richard, 1955-1959
  - Casale, Albert, 1942
  - Caspary, Vera, 1940-1941
  - Cassels, John, undated
  - Cassini, Igor
  - General Papers, 1959-1965
  - Clippings, 1963
  - Cayton, Revels, 1941-1946
  - Celler, Emanuel, 1940-1961
  - Cerf, Bennett, 1945-1957
  - Chambers, Whittaker, 1949-1970 (Box 597)
  - Chaplin, Charles, 1941-1955
  - Chapman, Emmanuel, 1946
  - Chase, Ilka, 1941
  - Chase, Stuart, 1953
  - Chatterjee, M.N., 1952
  - Chattle, Virgil, 1946
  - Chavez, Dennis, 1951
  - Cherne, Leo, 1947
  - Cherrington, Ben M., undated
  - Chevalier, Haakon, 1941
  - Chevalier, Maurice, 1951
  - Cheyfitz, Edward T., undated
  - Childress, Alice, 1956
  - Chodorov, Edward, undated
  - Chodorcv, Frank, 1950-1952
  - Chodorov, Jerome, 1940-1955
  - Christians, Mady, 1941-1945
  - Christoffel, Harold, 1949-1950
  - Christophorides, Demetrios, 1945
  - Clark, Joseph, 1946
  - Close, Upton, 1946-1951
  - Clubb, Edmund O., 1951
  - Cluka, Earl L., undated
  - Clurman, Harold, 1940
  - Coates, Robert M., 1940
  - Coff, Lee J., 1952
  - Coffee, John M., undated
  - Cole, Lester, 1940
  - Coleman, A.P., 1952
  - Collins, Charles, 1945-1946
  - Collins, Harold, 1945-1946
  - Colman, Louis, 1946
  - Colon, Jesus, 1946
  - Condon, Edward U., undated
  - Connelly, Marc, 1941 (Box 598)
  - Connelly, Philip, undated
  - Conniff, Frank, 1949
  - Connolly, Eugene P., 1946
  - Conroy, Jack, 1941
  - Conroy, James, undated
  - Coon, Boyd Warren, undated
  - Cooper, Esther, 1946
  - Copland, Aaron, 1950
  - Corcos, Lucille, 1964
  - Corelli, Alan, 1960
  - Corey, Paul, 1946-1952
  - Corwin, Norman, 1942-1950
  - Costello, Emil, 1941
  - Cotto-Thorner, Guillermo, 1946
  - Counts, George S., 1939
  - Cousins, Norman, 1947-1953
  - Covello, Leonard, 1946
  - Cowl, Margaret, 1936
  - Cowley, Malcolm, undated
  - Coy, Albert Wayne, undated
  - Craig, George N., 1950
  - Crain, Lucille Cardin, 1948-1951
  - Cranhshaw, Edward, 1950-1951
  - Cranston, Alan, undated
  - Crawford, Kenneth, 1942
  - Crawford, Matt, 1946
  - Crawford, Merritt, undated
  - Crichton, Kyle, 1938-1950
  - Cronin, Rev. John F., 1949
  - Crosby, Alexander L., 1941
  - Crosly, John, 1950-1952
  - Crouch, Paul, 1951-1952
  - Crouse, Russell, 1953
  - Crown, Joseph, 1946-1950
  - Crum, Bartley, 1944-1948
  - Culbertson, Ely, 1946
  - Cullen, Countee, 1940
  - Culp, Eugene M., 1953
  - Cunningham, Sarah, 1955
  - Curran, Joseph, 1940-1946 (Box 599)
  - Currie, Lauchlin, 1951
  - Curtain, Tom, 1941
  - Curtis, Elinor, 1936
  - Cuthbert, Marion, 1936
  - Cvetic, Matt, 1950
  - Da Silva, Howard, 1950
  - Dale, Thelma, 1946
  - Damon, Frances, 1946-1951
  - Dana, H.W.L., 1940-1941
  - Dassin, Jules, 1961
  - Davidman, Joy, 1940-1947
  - Davidson, Jo, 1945
  - Davies, Joseph E., 1944
  - Davis, Benjamin J., Jr., 1933-1949
  - Davis, David, 1944-1946
  - Davis, E.E., 1942
  - Davis, Elmer, undated
  - Davis, Frank Marshall, 1938-1949
  - Davis, Garry, undated
  - Davis, Jerome, 1938-1951
  - Davis, Lester, 1946
  - Dawber, Mark A., 1950
  - Dean, Elwood, 1946
  - De Boer, John, 1940-1950
  - DeCapua, Albert, 1947
  - Decavitch, Victor, 1944
  - Dehn, Adolf, undated
  - Delacy, Hugh, 1945-1946
  - Delaney, Thomas, 1946
  - Delong, Harley, 1942
  - Demaio, Ernest, 1943-1944
  - Dennis, Eugene, 1941-1948
  - Dennis, Lawrence, 1950-1956
  - Dermody, Joseph, undated
  - De Romero, Helen Vasquez, 1946
  - Deutsch, Albert, 1940
  - Dewald, Albert, 1940
  - Dichter, Irving, 1948
  - Dickerson, Earl B., 1946
  - Di Donato, Pietro, 1940-1941
  - Dies, Martin, 1938-1964
  - Diggis, Charles C., undated (Box 600)
  - Dilling, Elizabeth, 1947
  - Dimitroft, Georgi, 1937-1949
  - Dirksen, Everett, 1946
  - Dixon, Dean, 1945-1946
  - Djamgaroff, George, 1920-1951
  - Dmytryk, Edward, 1943-1951
  - Dobbs, Malcolm C., 1940-1946
  - Dodd, Bell V., 1940-1952
  - Dodd, Thomas J., 1960-1963
  - Doggett, E.L., 1942& undated
  - Dolivet, Louis, 1950-1952
  - Dombrowski, James A., 1946
  - Donawa, Arnold, 1946& undated
  - Donner, Frank, 1961
  - Donovan, Richard, undated
  - Doonping, R. and James M., 1932
  - Doriot, Jacques, undated
  - Dorlack, Joseph, 1942& undated
  - Dos Passos, John, 1930-1937
  - Douglas, Aaron, 1946
  - Douglas, Helen Gahagan, 1939-1950& undated
  - Douglas, Melvyn, 1938-1942& undated
  - Douglas, Paul, 1948
  - Douglas, William O., 1952
  - Douglass, Truman, 1955
  - Downes, Olin, 1946-1955
  - Doyle, Bernadette, undated
  - Draper, Muriel, 1937-1947
  - Draper, Paul, 1938-1950& undated (Box 601)
  - Dreher, Carl, 1952
  - Dreiser, Theodore, 1941-1946
  - Dublin, Mary, 1937-1940
  - Dubois, W.E.B., 1945-1963& undated
  - Ducuos, Jacques, 1945& undated
  - Dudley, Lt., undated
  - Dugan, James, 1941
  - Duke, Marie, 1938& undated
  - Dunjee, Roscoe, 1946& undated
  - Dunn, Leslie Clarence, 1957
  - Dunn, Robert W., 1933-1941
  - Dunne, Philip, 1939& undated
  - Duran, Gustavo, undated
  - Durkin, Henry P., 1967-1968& undated
  - Durkin, James H., undated
  - Durr, Clifford J., ca. 1938
  - Durr, Virginia Foster, 1940-1948& undated
  - D' Usseau, Arnaud, 1941-1946& undated
  - D' Usseau, Susan, undated
  - Dwyer, Thomas F., 1945& undated
  - Eaton, Cyrus, 1959-1961
  - Eaton, Walter Pritchard, 1940
  - Eberharter, Herman P., 1946
  - Ecklund, Walter K., 1946
  - Edelen, E. J., 1941
  - Edie, Mildred, 1937
  - Edwards, A.E., 1943& undated
  - Efron, Edith, 1972-1972
  - Eggert, Ken, 1938
  - Ehrenburg, Ilya, 1946
  - Einstein, Albert, 1948-1955& undated (Box 602)
  - Eisenberg, Frances R., 1951
  - Eisler, Gerhart, 1945-1947& undated
  - Eisler, Hanns, 1947& undated
  - Ekins, H. R., 1948
  - Elconin, William B., 1942& undated
  - Eldridge, Seba, 1946
  - Eliot, George Fielding, 1945
  - Eliot, Thomas H., 1942
  - Eliscu, Edward, 1940-1955
  - Eliscu, Stella Block, 1940
  - Ellison, Naomi, 1945
  - Ellison, Ralph, 1941
  - Elting, Mary, 1947& undated
  - Emerson, Haven, 1937-1949
  - Emerson, Thomas I., 1942-1949& undated
  - Emspak, Julius, 1938-1949& undated
  - Endore, Guy, 1940& undated
  - English, Robert, 1939-1940
  - Ensil, Robert, 1946
  - Ephraim, Jerome W., 1939
  - Epstein, Henry, 1941& undated
  - Epstein, Israel, 1946-1950
  - Ernst, Morris, undated
  - Erskine, John, 1950
  - Evans, C., 1942& undated
  - Evans, Ernestine, 1950
  - Evergood, Philip, 1937-1947& undated
  - Ezekiel, Mordecai, 1938-1945
  - Facci, Guiseppi, 1918-1937& undated
  - Fadiman, Clifton, 1932-1951
  - Fairbank, John K., 1966
  - Fairley, Barker, 1949
  - Faizer, Chuck, 1946
  - Farmer, Frances, 1938-1940& undated
  - Farmer, James, 1963
  - Fartag, James, 1944
  - Fast, Howard, 1948-1950& undated
  - Fath, Creekmore, 1942-1947
  - Faulk, John Henry, 1957
  - Faulkner, Stanley, 1946-1950
  - Fauset, Arthur Huff, 1946
  - Fay, Charles, 1941& undated
  - Fay, Frank, 1946-1961& undated (Box 603)
  - Fearing, Franklin, 1943
  - Fein, Bernard, undated
  - Feinberg, William, 1936-1946& undated
  - Feldkirchner, John, 1941
  - Felhaber, Elmer, 1940-1941& undated
  - Felsen, Henry, 1950-1951& undated
  - Felshin, Max, 1946& undated
  - Fenningston, Sylvia, undated
  - Ferber, Edna, 1937-1948
  - Ferguson, Harvey, 1940
  - Ferrer, Jose, 1951
  - Ferris, Vincent J., 1941
  - Feuchtwanger, Lion, 1943-1945& undated
  - Field, Ben, 1941
  - Field, Frederick V.
  - Miscellaneous, 1941& undated
  - Field, Frederick V.
  - Financial Papers, 1941
  - Field, Frederick V.
  - Financial Papers, 1942
  - Field, Frederick V.
  - Financial Papers, 1943
  - Field, Frederick V. (Box 604)
  - Financial Papers, 1944
  - Field, Frederick V.
  - Financial Papers, 1951
  - Field, Marshall, 1944-1950
  - Field, Noel, undated
  - Field, Sarah Bard, 1941
  - Fields, J., undated
  - Fields, Joe, 1941-1946
  - Fifield, James W., Jr., 1951-1952
  - Filner, Joseph, 1946
  - Fine, Benjamin, 1962
  - Fine, Fred, 1940-1946& undated
  - Finn, Milton, 1941
  - Fischer, Ruth, 1946& undated
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1949
  - Fishbein, Jack I., 1939-1940
  - Fisher, Charles, 1941-1947& undated
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1951-1955
  - Fisher, Welthy Honsinger, 1950
  - Fitzgerald, Albert, 1944-1946& undated
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas, 1947& undated
  - Flagstad, Kirsten, 1947& undated
  - Flanagan, Hallie, 1937
  - Flaxer, Abram, 1936-1946& undated
  - Flexer, Eleanor, 1940
  - Fliner, J. H., 1946
  - Fly, James L., 1947& undated
  - Flynn, Edward J., 1947
  - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley, 1940-1961
  - Foley, Martha, 1950
  - Foley, Thomas, 1942-1944& undated
  - Forbes, May, undated
  - Ford, George B., 1940-1947
  - Ford, James W., 1946
  - Foreman, Carl, 1955-1960
  - Foreman, Clark, 1946-1948& undated
  - Forman, Harrison, 1940-1952
  - Forsyth, Margaret, 1936-1938
  - Fortas, Abe, 1940-1965& undated
  - Foster, Joseph, 1946-1958
  - Foster, William Z., 1940-1951& undated
  - Foulk, Malcolm, 1946 (Box 605)
  - Fox, Mary, undated
  - Fox, Matty, 1949
  - Fox, Ruth, 1944
  - Fraenkel, Osmond K., 1952
  - Fraga, Vincent, 1941
  - Frank, Charles, 1939-1942& undated
  - Frank, Waldo, undated
  - Franklin, Julian, 1947
  - Franks, Charles, 1942& undated
  - Frantz, John M., 1936-1944
  - Frazier, E. Franklin, 1946& undated
  - Free, Lloyd, 1946& undated
  - Freedman, Benjamin H., 1948-1955
  - Freedman, Israel, 1946
  - Freedman, Malvina, 1943
  - Freeman, Frank N., undated
  - Freeman, Frank S., 1948-1949& undated
  - Freeman, Ruth, 1946
  - Freeman, Samuel, 1938
  - Freistadt, Hans, 1948-1949
  - Freund, Arthur J., 1950
  - Friedland, Bennie, 1946
  - Friedman, Henrietta, 1947
  - Friedman, Morton, 1947
  - Frisbie, Walter, 1946
  - Fritchman, Stephen H., 1946-1947
  - Funn, Dorothy K., 1946
  - Funt, Dorothy, 1943
  - Furry, Wendell, 1949
  - Gabriel, Gilbert, 1951
  - Gabriel, Helen, 1950
  - Gaer, Joseph, 1945-1946& undated
  - Gaeth, Arthur, 1948-1949
  - Gaffer, Herman, 1943
  - Gailmor, William, 1943-1949& undated
  - Gainor, Morris, 1941-1946
  - Gallo, John, 1945
  - Gandy, John M., 1946
  - Cannes, Harry, 1935-1938
  - Gannett, Lewis, 1921-1948
  - Cans, Helene, 1936
  - Gans, Sidney, undated
  - Gantt, W. Horsley, 1941
  - Garcia, Manuel, 1941
  - Gardner, Ava, 1954
  - Gardner, Bea, 1946
  - Gardner, Virginia, 1946
  - Garfield, Arthur, 1947
  - Garfield, John, 1937-1951 (Box 606)
  - Garfield, Nathan, 1941
  - Garland, Charles, undated
  - Garlin, Sender, 1941-1945
  - Garrett, Betty, 1943
  - Garretson, James, 1944
  - Garriga, Miguel, 1938-1951
  - Garrison, Lloyd K., 1942
  - Garry, James, 1941& undated
  - Garsson, Murray, 1946
  - Gates, John, 1946-1951
  - Gates, Lillian, 1945-1946
  - Gauld, Charles A., 1940& undated
  - Gaulden, Rose, 1946
  - Gavian, Ruth Wood, 1949
  - Gaylburd, Marcus, 1947
  - Gebert, William K., 1934
  - Geddes, Norman Bel, 1941
  - Geer, Will, 1937-1946
  - Geiger, Theodore, 1952& undated
  - Geiser, Carl, 1932-1946
  - Geisz, Henry, 1945
  - Gelbin, Gertrude, 1943
  - Gelfan, Samuel, 1948
  - Gellhorn, Martha, 1950-1953
  - Gellhorn, Walter F., 1939-1952& undated
  - Gemmill, Paul, 1939-1950& undated
  - George, Daisy S., 1946
  - Gershwin, Ira, 1941
  - Gerson, Si, 1946
  - Gibney, Sheridan, 1943
  - Gibson, Ernest, 1947
  - Gideonse, Harry D., 1947
  - Gieseking, Walter, 1949-1954& undated
  - Gilbert, Albert C., 1939
  - Gilbert, Jack, 1938
  - Gilbert, Richard Vincent, 1902
  - Gilbert, Ronnie, 1950
  - Gilbert, Sidney, 1944-1945
  - Gilford, Jack, 1948 (Box 607)
  - Gilkes, Lillian Barnard, 1941
  - Gillenson, Lew, 1953
  - Gilles, Earl, undated
  - Gilman, Mrs. Isaac, 1946
  - Gimbel, Elinor, 1941-1946& undated
  - Glazer, Tom, 1946-1948
  - Gleason, Leverett S., 1943-1944& undated
  - Glenn, Frank, 1961
  - Gliona, Will, 1934
  - Glueck, Sheldon, 1956
  - Goddard, Paulette, 1945
  - Godfrey, Catherine, 1946
  - Goebbels, Joseph, 1936
  - Goff, Irving, 1946
  - Goff, Sophie, 1946
  - Goffer, Hyman, 1946
  - Gold, Ben, 1928-1946
  - Gold, David, 1950
  - Gold, Michael, 1941
  - Gold, Philip, 1938
  - Goldberg, Hyman, 1951
  - Goldberg, Samuel, 1947
  - Goldblatt, Louis, 1946
  - Golden, B., 1950
  - Golden, John, 1946
  - Golden, William, 1945
  - Goldman, Harold, undated
  - Goldschmidt, Arthur E., 1938
  - Goldsmith, Arthur J., 1946-1951
  - Goldsmith, Leonard, 1940
  - Goldstein, Ben, 1933
  - Goldstein, Nina, 1946
  - Goldway, David, 1946
  - Golenkina, Vera, 1939
  - Golos, Fanny, 1946
  - Goltz, William, 1943
  - Gomez, William, 1943
  - Goodenough, Erwin R., 1943
  - Goodman, Edith, 1954
  - Goodman, John, 1946
  - Goodman, Johnnie, 1943
  - Goodstein, Albert, 1946
  - Gordon, Abe, 1943
  - Gordon, David, 1955
  - Gordon, Elizabeth, 1951
  - Gordon, Jesse, 1956
  - Gordon, Louis, undated
  - Gordon, Max, 1941-1946
  - Gordon, Michael, 1943
  - Gordon, Rosalie, 1956-1957
  - Gordon, Ruth, 1940
  - Gorelick, Jack, undated
  - Gorelik, Mordecai, 1943
  - Gorman, Francis J., 1938
  - Goslin, Willard, 1951
  - Gosling, Charles, 1937-1941
  - Goudsmit, Samuel, 1954
  - Gould, Morton, 1946
  - Gouzenko, Igor, 1947
  - Gow, James, 1945
  - Grabbe, Stanley, undated
  - Grabon, Boleslaw, undated
  - Grafton, Samuel, 1952
  - Graham, Betty, undated
  - Graham, Frank Porter, 1938-1949& undated (Box 608)
  - Graham, Martha, 1937
  - Graham, Shirley, 1947
  - Granger, Lester, 1946
  - Granich, Grace, 1946
  - Grant, Edmonia W., 1946
  - Grant, Morton, 1941
  - Grauer, Ben, 1942
  - Graves, Elsa, 1946
  - Graves, Mortimer, 1939-1941
  - Gray, Barry, 1952
  - Gray, Herman A., 1954
  - Gray, Justin, 1946
  - Gray, Lillian, 1950
  - Grayson, Mitchell, 1939
  - Greaza, Walter, ca. 1950s
  - Grecht, Rebecca, 1946
  - Green, Gil, 1937
  - Green, John, 1941
  - Green, Johnny, 1956& undated
  - Greene, Dave, 1946
  - Greenspun, Hank, 1953
  - Grenner, Martha, 1936
  - Griffin, Frank, 1945
  - Griffin, Irene, 1954
  - Griffith, Kelley E., undated
  - Griffith, Sanford, 1943
  - Grimm, Peter A., 1946
  - Griswold, Denny, 1950& undated
  - Grogan, William, 1946
  - Gropper, William, 1933-1946& undated
  - Gross, Chaim, 1937
  - Gross, Louis D., 1946
  - Grossbein, Simeon, 1946
  - Groth, John, 1946-1952
  - Grow, Robert W., 1952
  - Gruber, Ruth, 1938
  - Gruenberg, Sidonete M., 1946
  - Gruenwald, Henry W., 1951
  - Grundfest, Harry, undated
  - Gudinas, Julia, undated
  - Guggenheimer, Mrs. J. C., 1939
  - Gulotta, Frances, 1945
  - Gumberg, Alexander, 1941& undated
  - Gumpel, Morris, 1943
  - Gundlach, Ralph H., 1939-1949& undated
  - Gunther, John, undated
  - Gunther, Lynn, 1942& undated
  - Guttko, Erwin A., 1947
  - Gwathmey, Robert, 1941
  - H. 1955, 1966
  - Hagen, Uta, 1942
  - Haldane, J.B.S., 1947
  - Hale, William Harlan, 1958
  - Hall, Gordon, undated
  - Hall, Gus, 1937-1962
  - Hall, Helen, 1941& undated
  - Hall, Josephine, 1954
  - Haller, William Jr., 1950
  - Halmy, Margaret, 1951
  - Halper, Albert, 1934-1950
  - Halpern, Eli, 1943
  - Halpern, Harry, 1950
  - Halsey, Margaret, 1960
  - Hamblin, Donald W., 1961
  - Hamel, Richard, 1945-1950& undated
  - Hamilton, Samuel L., 1941
  - Hamilton, W., undated
  - Hamlin, Talbot, ca. 1950s (Box 609)
  - Hammer, Armand, 1970
  - Hammett, Dashiell, 1938-1941& undated
  - Hammond, John Henry, Jr., 1933-1947& undated
  - Hammond, Mrs. John, Jr., undated
  - Hanan, Norma, undated
  - Hand, Learned, 1953
  - Handy, W.C., 1955
  - Haney, Lewis, 1949
  - Hanson, Elisha, 1940
  - Hanson, Haldore, undated
  - Hapgood, Powers, 1944
  - Harburg, E.Y., 1943
  - Hargis, Billy James, 1957
  - Harisiades, Peter, 1947
  - Harper, William, 1947
  - Harris, Bertha, 1950
  - Harris, Kay, 1936
  - Harris, Larry, 1950
  - Harris, Sanford, 1950
  - Harris, Vera, undated
  - Harrison, Earl G., undated
  - Harrison, George, 1946
  - Harrison, Robert, 1947
  - Harrison, William, 1946
  - Hart, Henry, 1940-1941
  - Hart, Moss, 1952
  - Hartley, Harold, ca. 1938
  - Hartnett, Vincent, 1949-1950& undated
  - Hartwick, Tolley, undated (Box 610)
  - Hasson, Isaac, 1939
  - Hastie, William H., 1946
  - Hathaway, Clarence, 1939-1946& undated
  - Hathaway, Dr. Marion, 1951
  - Haug, Fred, 1935-1946
  - Hausman, Samuel, 1946
  - Havens, Selwyn, 1938
  - Havighurst, Robert J., 1945-1949& undated
  - Hawes, Elizabeth, 1954
  - Hawley, Peter K., 1932
  - Hayes, Helen, 1946
  - Hayes, Jack, 1946
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1950
  - Hays, Lee, 1938-1955& undated
  - Haywood, Allan S., 1938
  - Hayworth, Rita, 1955
  - Hazlitt, Henry, 1949-1951
  - Healy, Ned R., 1946
  - Hearst, William Randolph, 1934-1942& undated
  - Hebert Ernest, 1946
  - Hecht, Ben, 1941-1954
  - Hecht, Harold, 1955-1962
  - Hedrick, E.H., 1946
  - Hedrick, Travis, 1943
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 1957
  - Heinz, H.J., undated
  - Heller, A.A., 1944-1946& undated
  - Heller, Edna Eby, 1962
  - Heller, Robert, 1950
  - Hellerman, Freddie, 1950
  - Hellgren, Nora, 1943
  - Hellman, Esther, 1938
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1937-1938
  - Helm, Harold H., 1946
  - Helstein, Ralph, 1946
  - Hemingway, Ernest, 1950-1955& undated
  - Henderson, Algo D., 1949
  - Henderson, Donald, 1933-1941& undated
  - Henderson, William R., 1946
  - Hendley, Charles J., 1940
  - Hennock, Frieda, 1932-1948
  - Henry, Charles, 1949& undated
  - Henry, David, 1947
  - Henry, Lillian, 1936
  - Henry, Lyndon, 1946
  - Herbert, F. Hugh, 1947-1951
  - Herbert, R. Lloyd, 1941 (Box 611)
  - Herbst, Frank, 1943
  - Herbst, Josephine, 1936-1940
  - Herrmann, John, undated
  - Hersey, John, 1945-1960& undated
  - Hewitt, Alan, undated
  - Heym, Stefan, 1936
  - Higinbotham, W.A., undated
  - Hiken, Nat, 1955
  - Hill, Charles A., 1946
  - Hill, George G., 1961
  - Hill, T. Arnold, 1935
  - Hiller, Helen, 1960
  - Hillman, Sidney, 1944-1946& undated
  - Hilton, James, 1941
  - Hilton, Ned, 1953
  - Himoff, Mary, 1946
  - Hinckley, William W., 1936
  - Hindus, Maurice, 1931-1952
  - Hirsch, Carl, 1951
  - Hirsch, Joseph, 1951-1955
  - Hirschberg, Herbert, 1947
  - Hirschmann, Ira A., ca. 1945-1949& undated
  - Hiskey, Dr. Clarence, 1951
  - Hiss, Alger, 1949-1961
  - Hlavaty, Julius, 1956
  - Hockenberry, Thomas W., 1947
  - Hoffman, Paul G., 1951-1956
  - Hoffman, Richard, 1955
  - Holifield, Chet, 1946 (Box 612)
  - Hollander, Louis, 1946
  - Holman, Helen, 1936
  - Holman, Libby, 1938
  - Holmes, Ehgene C., 1941
  - Holmes, Olive C., 1951
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1950
  - Holt, Dr. Arthur, 1951
  - Hook, Sidney, 1949
  - Hooker, West, 1951-1955& undated
  - Hopkins, Miriam, 1941
  - Hoptman, Gus, 1943
  - Horn, Samson, 1947& undated
  - Home, Lena, 1945-1947
  - Horowitz, A. Keane, 1946
  - Horowitz, Vladimir, 1955
  - Hosky, Charles S., 1948
  - Horsley, G. William, undated
  - Horton, Alice, 1946-1947
  - Horton, Helen, 1945
  - Houston, W.S., 1948
  - Houseman, John, 1937
  - Hovde, Bryn J., 1943
  - Howard, Elizabeth, 1951
  - Howard, George H., 1941
  - Howard, Milton, 1946& undated
  - Howard, Sidney, undated
  - Howe, Quincy, 1938
  - Huber, John, 1947
  - Huberman, Leo, 1946
  - Hudson, Charles B., 1955
  - Hudson, Claude, 1946
  - Hudson, Roy, 1937
  - Hughes, George F., 1939
  - Hughes, Howard, 1952
  - Hughes, Lanston, 1925-1950
  - Hull, Morgan, undated
  - Humboldt, Charles, 1946
  - Humphreys, Robert, 1949& undated
  - Humphries, Rolfe, 1954
  - Hunt, H.L., 1963-1965& undated
  - Hunt, Henry T., 1933
  - Hunt, Marsha, 1951
  - Hunter, Kent, 1951
  - Hunter, Oscar, 1946
  - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1940
  - Hunton, W.A., ca. 1940s
  - Hurst, Fannie, 1939-1961
  - Hurwitz, Leo T., undated
  - Huston, John, 1938-1949
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1949-1953& undated
  - Hutchinson, Dorothy, 1958
  - Ibanez, Frank, 1946 (Box 613)
  - Ickes, Harold L., 1946& undated
  - Imes, Mrs. W.L., 1936
  - Inman, Samuel Guy, 1941
  - Isacson, Leo, 1946-1948
  - Isaacs, Harold, 1947
  - Isaacs, Stanley M., 1938-1949& undated
  - Iselin, O'Donnell, 1946
  - Isserman, Abraham J., 1923-1940& undated
  - Ives, Burl, 1949-1952
  - Izac, Ed V., 1946
  - Jack, Hulan E., 1943-1946
  - Jackson, Ada B., 1946
  - Jackson, Cliff, 1960
  - Jackson, Joseph Henry, undated
  - Jackson, Luther P., 1963
  - Jackson, William, 1951
  - Jacobs, Lewis, 1943
  - Jaccbson, Muriel, 1946
  - Jacoby, Annalee, 1949
  - Jaeckel, Albert F., 1946
  - Jaffe, Harry, 1943
  - Jaffe, Henry, 1942-1950
  - Jaffe, Philip J., 1937-1950
  - Jaffe, Sam, 1937-1945& undated
  - James, Oscar, 1946
  - Janeway, Eliot, undated
  - Janowicz, William, 1947
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1961-1962
  - Jenkins, Dave, 1946
  - Jenner, William E., 1950-1955& undated
  - Jernagin, W.H., 1939-1946
  - Jerome, V.J., 1932& undated
  - Jessup, Philip C., 1940-1951& undated
  - Jett, Al, 1946 (Box 614)
  - Joewinski, Sigmond, undated
  - Johnson, Alvin S., 1955
  - Johnson, Arnold, undated
  - Johnson, Chic, 1955
  - Johnson, Clifford, 1941
  - Johnson, Crockett, 1946
  - Johnson, Dorothy, 1951
  - Johnson, Edwin C., 1955
  - Johnson, Gerald W., 1955
  - Johnson, Hewlett, 1945-1948
  - Johnson, Howard, 1946
  - Johnson, James Weldon, 1955
  - Johnson, Josephine W., 1940
  - Johnson, Martin, 1955
  - Johnson, Mary, 1936
  - Johnston, Eric, 1947
  - Joliot-Curie, Frederic, 1945-1946
  - Jones, Claudia, 1948
  - Jones, David D., 1946
  - Jones, Dora, 1941& undated
  - Jones, James, 1946
  - Jones, Richard, 1946
  - Joselow, Morris, undated
  - Josephs, Ray, 1954
  - Josephson, Emanuel M., 1946
  - Josephson, Leon, 1947
  - Josephson, Matthew, 1932-1941
  - Joyce, Hugh L., 1947
  - Judd, Walter H., 1948
  - Judth, Ernst, undated
  - Julienelle, Joseph, 1942
  - Jurich, J.F., 1937-1941
  - Jurist, Irma, 1936
  - Justin, Jules J., 1954
  - K. 1968-1969
  - Kahn, Albert E., 1944-1950
  - Kahn, Arthur D., ca. 1950
  - Kahn, Gordon, 1941
  - Kahn, I., 1943
  - Kallet, Arthur, 1935-1962& undated
  - Kaltenborn, H.V., 1938-1955
  - Kalven, Harry, 1955
  - Kamen, Martin D., 1957
  - Kamp, Joseph P., 1937-1949& undated
  - Kamp, Louis, 1950
  - Kandel, Terry, 1946
  - Kang, Younghill S., 1950
  - Kanin, Fay, 1950
  - Kanin, Carson, 1945-1958
  - Kanin, Michael, 1950
  - Kantarowicz, Alfred, 1947
  - Kantor, Samuel, 1944-1946